biomedlinks.com 2005-04-08

# <%TITLE%> - <%CAT_NAME%>

Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What information do we collect and how do we use it?**  
When you submit a URL, we need to know your name, e-mail address, this allows us to contact you if there is a question about a listing.

We may also use the information we collect to **** occasionally **** notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new products or services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable.

**What about "Cookies"?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies.

**Will BioMedLInks disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
BioMedLinks does not currently sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future. Also, BioMedLinks may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to third-party vendors, but these statistics currently include no personally identifying information.

**Your consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by BioMedLinks. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post our revised policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. **By using our site, you also agree to our Terms of Use. BioMedLinks is not liable for any direct, indirect, special, consequential or other damages that may arise form any violation of this Policy.**

**Tell us what you think**  
BioMedLinks welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send e-mail to Support@BioMedLinks.com .
